# TOH HAN SHIN, **JERRY**

Jerrytoh93@gmail.com ✓

https://www.linkedin.com/in/toh-han-shin-jerry-236406118/ in



9765 3869 📞

https://github.com/JerryTohHS



Passionate and motivated IT enthusiast with a strong work ethic and collaborative mindset. A firm believer in lifetime learning, I am constantly challenging myself through picking up new technology skills and coding languages. In my leisure time, I enjoy playing basketball, drawing from my experience as a former vice captain of my school team, and pursuing photography as a creative hobby.

## **KEY SKILLS & STRENGTHS**

Personal		Technical		Languages
- Leadership	- Stakeholder	- HTML	- Express	- English
- Teamwork	Management	- CSS	- Node	- Mandrain
- Communication		- Javascript	- SQL	- Hokkien
- Adaptability		- React		

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

# Senior Executive, Leasing & Marketing | Cathay Organisation Holdings Ltd

#### AUG 2022 - PRESENT

- Lead end-to-end management of Cathay Lifestyle App Enhancement and spearheaded 7 areas that improves user interface and user experience.
- Oversee full spectrum of property leasing management, such as property tax matters, credit control, acquiring new leases and negotiation of lease renewals for commercial and co-working space.
- Manage leasing and operations of Cathay's co-working space and improved occupancy rate by 20%.
- Assist in marketing initiatives for Cathay properties.
- Build and manage relationships with tenants and external agent.

## Senior Executive, Commercial Leasing | Singapore Land Authority

### SEP 2021 - AUG 2022

- Implement leasing strategies and plans for commercial properties.
- Develop deeper understanding of customer needs regarding space requirements and utilisation, and rental assistance.
- Manage tenant/ Managing Agent relationships and negotiate lease renewals.
- Formulate and review leasing policies and processes and arrears management.
- Coordinate property maintenance and repair works with contractors/managing agents.

# Associate, Policy & Promotion, Quality & Excellence Group | Enterprise Singapore

### OCT 2020 - SEP 2021

- Promoting adoption of high-value standards to help enterprises unlock opportunities in new sub-sectors and markets.
- Engaging key industry partners to encourage enterprises to adopt standards as a vital part of capability building.
- Equipping workforce with knowledge and competencies in leveraging quality and excellence as strategic business tools through outreach and industry engagements.

# **Business Development Executive | Lek San Construction Pte Ltd**

#### SEP 2019 - AUG 2020

- Orchestrated business development efforts, devising tailored sales strategies, nurturing client relationships, and providing solutions to meet client needs while contributing to administrative functions.
- Assumed Port Facility Security Officer role, comprehensively managing duties as per ISPS Code, including PFSP development, maintenance, and oversight for robust port security.

## Planning Engineer | STMicroelectronics Pte Ltd

#### OCT 2018 - SEP 2019

- Intervenes at all levels of the supply chain to expedite the process to support customer critical delivery.
- Frequent collaboration with Customer-Sales-Planning to enable optimisation of capacity and to meet customer demand.
- Analyse what-if scenario based on capacity and material availability and share the best delivery plan.
- Work closely with manufacturing to drive output delivery performance.
- Quickly respond to demand changes & ensure manufacturing stays on track with the changes made.

### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

## **Software Engineering | Rocket Academy**

NOV 2022 - NOV 2023

Certifications:

https://credsverse.com/credentials/21f0ee52-a478-4367-8b36-23686c6013cbhttps://learn.rocketacademy.co/student/certificates/YRPC1NB1GYYT/

- Frontend Development: HTML, CSS, React, Bootstrap, Material UI.
- Backend Development: Firebase, Express, Node, SQL, PostgreSQL, Sequelize.
- Others: Git, Github, Auth0.

## **Key Projects:**

- Project Mamak: A food ordering app featuring the best mamak foods. (https://capstone-mamak.vercel.app/)
- Project Booked: A reservation app to book your restaurants. (https://classy-tartufo-5da9c4.netlify.app/)
- Project Spork: The ultimate tool to search and organise your recipes. (<a href="https://thespork-b06ef.web.app/auth/login">https://thespork-b06ef.web.app/auth/login</a>)
- Project Ice Box: An app that not only offers an extensive library of recipes but also generates personalised dishes based on your fridge's contents. (https://lel010.github.io/project1-bootcamp-icebox/)
- Project Blackjack: A simplified version of the game Blackjack. (https://jerrytohhs.github.io/basics-blackjack/)
- Project Beat That: Players create the largest number they can by concatenating random dice roll digits. (https://jerrytohhs.github.io/basics-beat-that/)

# Degree of Bachelor of Engineering (Materials Engineering), Honours (Merit) with a Specialisation in Innovation and Intellectual Property | Nanyang Technological University

2015 - 2018

Second Class (Lower) Honors

Final Year Project: Characterisation and Microstructural Study of Titanium and Nickel Alloy in Cold Spray Technology

## Diploma in Chemical & Biomolecular Engineering | Ngee Ann Polytechnic

2010 - 2013

Graduating GPA: 3.55/4.00